cheeseandburger.com 2019-06-06

# Cheese & Burger Society

## INTRODUCTION

The policies below are intended to clearly inform our users about our privacy practices and procedures and are applicable to CheeseAndBurger.com. As part of the registration, operation and customization features of CheeseAndBurger.com, we gather certain types of information from users. We would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with them, and how to correct or change the information. Please review this privacy policy when you enter the website to keep aware of any policy changes.

CheeseAndBurger.com uses third parties such as agencies and e-mail service providers to manage content and e-mail delivery services on our site. When you submit information through our site, we may share your personally identifiable information as necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes. 

## INFORMATION COLLECTED BY CHEESEANDBURGER.COM

CheeseAndBurger.com collects two types of information from users: personal data such as name, phone, and e-mail addresses; and non-personal data such as information about traffic patterns on CheeseAndBurger.com (for example, how many users log on to CheeseAndBurger.com on a daily basis).

## PERSONAL DATA

Some personal data such as name, phone, postal address, e-mail address and business type are collected during registration or through other form submissions on our site.

## NON-PERSONAL DATA

Some data we collect contains non-personal information. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site or advertisement. We may use this information for various purposes, including system administration and enhancement and to collect information about the volume of use of different features available on CheeseAndBurger.com.

## CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

CheeseAndBurger.com has no intention of collecting personal information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13). If a child has provided us with personal information, CheeseAndBurger.com asks that a parent or guardian of the child contact CheeseAndBurger.com at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) if they would like the information submitted by a child deleted from our database. CheeseAndBurger.com will use reasonable efforts to delete such information from its database.

## COOKIES

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. CheeseAndBurger.com uses cookies to collect information. Cookies allow CheeseAndBurger.com to measure activity on the site and to make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. Cookies are used to improve your user experience. For example, the cookie allows you to have the option of saving your user name and password which eliminates the need for you to enter the information every time you visit CheeseAndBurger.com. (We do not recommend saving your user name and password if you use your computer in a shared environment.) In addition, our site may request the cookie from your browser so that we can retrieve the stored personal information to fill out forms so you do not have to manually enter the information each time. We may also store data on your cookie based on options you make on certain forms to enable us to customize information based on your criteria.

Please note that with most browsers, a user can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also usually set the browser not to accept cookies at all. By not accepting cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all features of CheeseAndBurger.com.

## USE OF INFORMATION

CheeseAndBurger.com uses both the personal and non-personal information we collect for a variety of purposes. For example, we use your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better products and service. Specifically, we use your information to communicate back to you, to update you on programs, services and benefits, and to personalize our web site for you. We also use the non-personal information to provide aggregate data reports to our Board of Directors and other interested parties. CheeseAndBurger.com uses third parties such as agencies and e-mail service providers to manage content and e-mail delivery services on our site. When you submit information through our site, we may share your personally identifiable information as necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes.

## SECURITY

CheeseAndBurger.com is committed to taking reasonable steps to ensure the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## YOUR CONSENT

By using this web site, you consent to our use of your personal and non-personal data as specified above. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## CONCERNS AND COMMENTS

Your privacy concerns are important to us. Please e-mail us with any further questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to:

Wisconsin Milk Marketing Board, Inc.  
C/O CheeseAndBurger.com   
8418 Excelsior Drive  
Madison, Wisconsin 53717   
Phone: 608-836-8820

Cheese & Burger Society is a registered service mark of the Wisconsin Milk Marketing Board, Inc.
